(Howard:)-Really?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)You're either with me or against me.
(Amy:)You want to take the bus to work?
(Sheldon:)Maybe there's a third option.
(Amy:)FYI, I had a doughnut
for breakfast, you jerk.
(Leonard:)So now we're just waiting
for the data
(Leonard:)from the ship to be crunched, but the
numbers look pretty promising.
(Howard:)That's so great. If you guys prove
the existence of Unruh radiation--
Hey, hey, hey!
My eyes are up here.
(Sheldon:)Howard, Raj, Judas.
(Penny:)You know what?
You're a crazy person.
(Sheldon:)A crazy person with a long memory,
(Sheldon:)and if all goes according to plan,
a robot army.
(Bernadette:)-Stop it.
-Or a mutant army.
(Sheldon:)It depends on how
my Kickstarter goes.
I said stop it!
(Howard:)Now, listen to me.
(Howard:)You two aren't just friends.